Guide to the Parker James Gillespie, Jr. Papers SC1160
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Parker James Gillespie, Jr. papers
1974-1998
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Gillespie, Parker James, Jr.
SC1160
12 Linear Feet
Information about Access
The materials are open for research use. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Scope and Contents
The materials consist of computer manuals, program documentation, and computer discs.
Educational technology.; Gillespie, Parker James, Jr.
- Papers, 1974-1998
  - Principles of Operation 05/390 POP, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Enterprises System Architecture/390, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Submit, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - PL/X, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Spires, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Labeler, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Com, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Oruyl, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Wylbur Exec Files, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Extended Exec Files, 1987 Dec (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Orvyl /370, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Using Tapes @ SCIP, 1978-1987 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Global Resource Sharing, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Apple, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - System Control Blocks, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Terminals for Managers, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Wylbur, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Brafgen Automated Tape Library, 1982 Aug (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Campus 170/168 System Spec, 1975 July 10 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Apple 6502 Assembler/Editor, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Apple II Basic Programming Manual, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - The DOS Manual, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Apple II Reference Manual, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Apple Pascal Reference Manual, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Applesoft II Basic Programming Reference Manual, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Spires Protocols, 1979 Apr (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Scip Standards, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Wylbur, 1975-1977 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Toca Memo, 1987-1999 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Spires Formats, 1988 Aug 14 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Unlabeled Folder with Office Memos, 1976-1986 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Security, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Orvyl, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Unlabeled Folder (Magazine Cutouts and Newsletters), 1981 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Orvyl Theory Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Orvyl Critiques, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Unlabeled Folder (Graphs and Campus Computing Bulletins), 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - SYSA CPU Projection/Reduction, 1994-1996 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Masters - Orvyl/370 Review, 1974 Sep (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Orvyl Program Event Recording, undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Tape Standards - Rejected Products, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Orvyl File Admin, undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - SPASM User Guide #064, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Orvyl, 1977-1979 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - T L M S, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Orvyl File System, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Tape Standards - Notes & Memos, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Terminal Communcators and File Transfer Utilities, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Wizard (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Computer files (floppy disks, 5 1/4"), 46 computer media (Box 2)
  - Users Manual, 1972 Mar (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - J. Powell - Users Manual, 1970 Oct (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Enterprise Architecture Version 1.0, 1996 Jun (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Text Editing in Wylbur Tutorial, 1993 Jan (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Loose papers - Technical notes (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - OS/VS Message Library: VS2 System Codes, 1981 June (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - WYLBUR File Manual, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Page WYLBUR for Novice Terminal Users, 1986 Feb. (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Samson, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - MacSamson Card-Master, undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Quick Guide to Samson (IBM PC Version II), 1984 Sept. (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Samson Diskettes 2.00 #680, 1984-1986 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Samson for the HP 150 Version 1.1, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Stanford@Work News, 200 Fall (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Calendars, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Blank Folders, undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Introducing SCIP, DVDit! User Manual, HMS Handley, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - PAGE WYLBUR PRIMER, 1982 Dec. (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - ORVYL User's Guide, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - WYLBUR EXEC File Manual, 1982 Oct. (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Using WYLBUR Mail, 1984 Dec. (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Using WYLBUR Manual, 1983 April, 1981 Dec., 1980 Feb (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - WYLBUR User's Guide, 1984 Sept. (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - WYLBUR User's Guide #424, 1983 Oct., 1981 March (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - WYLBUR Overview #415, 1984 Dec. (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - EZYWYLBUR #417, 1984 Jan.and Oct., 1983 April, 1982 Jan. and Aug., 1981 Aug, 1980 Oct. (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Terminals & Communications, 1983 Oct., 1982 March and Aug., 1977 Sept. (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Using BATWYL at Stanford #409, 1982 Aug., 1979 Nov. (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - WYLBUR Exec File Tutorial #276, 1976 June 1 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Exec File Processing #267, 1980 April (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - ORVYL/370 Dunc. Desc #264 Sections 5.6 thru 5.14 Macro's, 1975 Oct. (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - ORVYL/FORTRAN User's Guide #250, 1981, 1977 Dec. (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - ORVYL/370: Functional Descrip. #246 (History Files), 1983 Sept., 1975 Oct. (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - WYLBUR Reference Card #232, 1984 Oct., 1983 March, 1978 Feb. (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - WYLBUR Ref man #234, 1984 Sept. (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - WYLBUR Reference Manual #234, 1984 March (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - ORVYL II, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - ORVYL/Sort OBS/Hist File #217, 1985 May, 1983 Sept. (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - WYLBUR/370 Reference Manual #234, 1977 April (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - WYLBUR Reference Manual #234 (OBS), 1981 Oct. (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - WYLBUR Reference Manual #234, 1983 May (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Structured Programming With Go To Statements, 1974 May (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Cobol Language Specifications, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Fortran (Full) + Prog. Guide, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - PL/I Fortran IV Compiler Program Logic Manual, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Principles of Operations, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Various Papers (Cal Poly Graphics Routine, Mix Simulation, Books on Systems Theories, Capabilities of Brandon Applied Systems, 1971-1975 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Using Submit #190, 1982 Aug. (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Using Submit #190, 1981 Jan., 1980 Dec., 1976 Sept. (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Sign #166, 1976 Feb., 1975 May (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - File Definer (Spires) #487 hist/Obs, 1983 July, 1982 Nov. (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Orvyl File System: A Simple Guide #102, 1978 March (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Guide to Status Display #90, 1984 Nov. (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - SPASM #64, 1973 April 1 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Scip Scoop, 1975-1978 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - User's Guide to SVCCOM, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - WYLBUR Exec File Manual #569, 1983 Nov. (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - System3370 Assembler Language Programming, 1977 Jan. 7 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - WYLBUR Exec File Command, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - ORVYL User's Guide #511, 1982 April (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Standards, 1978 Sept. (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Spitbol, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Model Terminal, 1968, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - The Application Transition Process Guide Book, 1997 Aug. (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Proposal for the Purchase of Stanford University IBM 360/67, undated (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Proposal for CALCOMP 7110 Mass Storage Automatic Tape Library System, 1978 March 31 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Bulletin Computation Center - Campus Facility, 1971-1973 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - A Simple Axiomatic Basis for Programming Language Constructs, 1973 May 8 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Around the Office, 1989-1992 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - In Touch, 1995-1997 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Speaking of Computers, 1991-2000 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - HIBAL Manual, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - ORVYL/370, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Campus Computing Bulletin, 1978-1980 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Sculp Scoop, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - SLAC Vm Notebook, 1983 July 20 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - How to Write an IOS Driver, undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - IBM System/370 Extended Architecture Interpretive Execution, 1984 Jan. (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - IE BUPDTX User's Guide, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Systems Consulting technical Topics, 1979 May (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - How to Use the STARTICO Macro, 1989 Aug. 24 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - The Emulator Software Assignment, 1997 May 9 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Memos, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Memos, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Tape Use, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Memos, 1979-1982 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Memos, 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Memos, 1979-1983 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Computer files (floppy disks, 5 1/4") (Box 7)